playmillion1.com 2016-01-17

# Privacy Policy - Play Online Casino with up to 3000€ Welcome Bonus - PlayMillion.com

PlayMillion.com values and respects the privacy of each and every one of its members, which we safeguard through our Privacy Policy. Please take the time to read the contents of this policy and familiarize yourself with its contents.

### Security

PlayMillion.com goes to great lengths to guarantee that your personal and financial information remains 100% secure and confidential. We employ industry standard security protocols (128 bit, SSL data encryption technology) to ensure that all transactions including deposits and withdrawals are carried out in a totally secure manner. This technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than PlayMillion.com while it is being transmitted between you and PlayMillion.com.

### Personal Information

As part of the PlayMillion.com registration process, we ask for a number of personal details, including your first and last name, physical and billing address as well as e-mail address and date of birth. We will need this information to open your account, to process transactions and for customer service purposes. Rest assured that under no circumstances will we pass on or sell these details to a third party. This information may also be used in conjunction with your private Username and Password to verify your identity. The only exception to this policy is if you have a big win – then we may use your username and/or first name for promotional purposes.

### What are Cookies?

Cookies are small files containing information that enables a website to track its visitors. To enable PlayMillion.com to find out which advertisement brought you to our website, we may use the PlayMillion.com cookies on your computer. In the event that we do collect such information, you will remain personally unidentifiable and we will not share this information with any unconnected third party.

### Advertising System

The PlayMillion.com advertising system logs IP addresses in order to supply more accurate marketing features, such as language specific banners. It does NOT record any e-mail addresses, so rest assured that you will not receive any spam mail as a result of giving us your address.

### User Responsibility

As a member of PlayMillion.com, you are solely responsible for all actions taken using your PlayMillion.com account. We advise you to keep your Username and Password secret at all times: under no circumstances should you give out this sensitive information to other players at PlayMillion.com or anywhere else online or offline. If for some reason you believe that your Username or Password have been compromised in any way, you should notify the PlayMillion.com Customer Support team immediately.

### Limits of Confidentiality

For legal reasons, PlayMillion.com may be required under certain circumstances to disclose your personal information. Reasons for this may include:

1\. to protect and defend our rights or property  
2\. to comply with any legal process served on us. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information, including player identification, name, physical address, billing address, e-mail and/or phone number, to third parties as we believe necessary or appropriate in connection with any investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or any other unlawful or prohibited activity that might expose us to legal liability.

PlayMillion.com may occasionally make changes to the above Privacy Policy. Any such changes will be posted on this page and it is the responsibility of the player to visit this page on a regular basis in order to stay informed of changes that may occur. If you have any questions or concerns regarding security and privacy, please do not hesitate to contact our 24/7 Customer Support Team at any time, and they will be happy to assist you.
